

CONTACT ME AT

- 32/42A
 Naberezhnyye Chelny, 423832
 Russian Federation
- calebjason90@gmail.com
- https://calebkanku.netlify.app
- in

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Communication Skills
- • • Fast Learner
- •••• Ability to Work in a Team
- •••• Curriculum and
- ••• Computer Skills
- ••• Effective Time
 Management

AWARDS RECEIVED

Outstanding Employee of the Year, English world (2019)

CALEB KANKU

WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Full stack developer graduated from the Federal University of Kazan, with 2 years+ of work experience as an IT consultant. Computer buff, I learned to code in various computer languages (C #, Python, Javascript) and created personal projects, including an online marketplace that allows sellers to sell on the platform, a netflix clone, Rest APIs with Django . Versatile, I master the different technical stages of creating a site or a web application; from understanding user needs, to frontend and backend development using React/Nextjs, NodeJs and Django which i specialize in. I teach programming to college and high school students.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Programming Teacher

AIS | Sept 2021 - present

- Implemented python lessons in Robotics classes
- introduced Computer science, Machine learning, and Neural network concepts to high-school students.

IT Consultant

English world | sept 2017 - Nov 2020

- Ran analysis of the IT system and infrastructure of the company.
- Diagnosed problems, inefficiencies, and weaknesses of the IT system.
- fixed bugs on the company website

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Kazan Federal University

Bachelor in Computer science | sept 2017 - July 2021

St Germain high school

Scientific section | 2010 - 2014